{
    "id": "af5835ec13fd419eb24414f7a4d8b20e",
    "title": "Who, Which, That",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The police are searching for the man ………………………… abducted the child.",
            "description": "Use who to refer to people and which to refer to things. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the book ………………………….. I was talking about.",
            "description": "Either which or that can refer to things in identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know anyone ………………………. can repair my camera?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The jewels ……………………….. the heiress wore were very expensive.",
            "description": "Either which or that can refer to things in identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The flowers ………………………… adorn the dais are artificial.",
            "description": "Either which or that can refer to things in identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The athlete ………………………… ankle was broken might need surgery.",
            "description": "Whose can refer to both people and things. Use it to replace pronouns in the possessive case.",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "who",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The parrot …………………………. wings are broken may not fly ever again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whose",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The clown ……………………….. antics amused everyone was not happy in his life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whose",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The microwave oven …………………………… I bought for Christmas was not very expensive.",
            "description": "Either which or that can refer to things in identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Athletes ………………………… practice everyday are more likely to win.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house …………………………..  I inherited from my grandfather.",
            "description": "Either which or that can refer to things in identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The lion killed the deer ………………………….. was drinking water from the stream.",
            "description": "Either which or that can refer to things in identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}